so my wife and I been married 20 years
[Applause]
she's my high school sweetheart yeah we
got married 1998 and in 2002 my mom
remarried an American fella known as my
father-in-law
I couldn't tell who got that first I
didn't realize there was a whole bunch
of Alabama fans here roll tide
that's pretty cool man sorry so my wife
is actually technically she's my sister
I am my own brother-in-law which means I
call myself if I need help moving it's
my stuff
raising two beautiful nephews
and the safety czar back on the gun so
thank you very much
that's awesome papa he's one of us
[Music]
[Applause]
we were worried about him for a little
while you know he said he's back there's
nothing okay we can put it down but I
can keep my safety on the whole murder
sister all right now we're gonna deal
with this problem right here it's
awesome so my wife is actually hearing
the audience love her so much she
supports my comedy and sports this dream
of ours together and let me tell you how
this happens is we have this king-sized
mattress which provides distance right
when you first get together you're
thinking home man this is she's hot and
he's hot we're hot together this is
great
but three years into it it's a different
kind of hot she turns into something I
don't know karate master in bed it's
like me hot
and I just want to cuddle so bad and I
can't even kiss her goodnight I really
can't because she's like three barrel
rolls away
I don't have the core muscles um I think
that happen I love you
we just have five it out and I wanted to
kiss her goodnight man I've got to do
the whole centrifugal force thing you
know where yeah yeah get you anchor with
the the headboard with one hand to get
that one leg out how to do that hip bump
and just start rolling made way through
the first roll the CPAP goes
but things are great it makes fun of of
a man they are useful they are amazing
like anytime like you're in the hospital
or something and and they have a lie son
like I had a back surgery in December
and which didn't work but anyway so I'm
in the bed and pain and they're always
in there in and out of there and so I
finally just take the sheet and put it
over my head cuz you know snorkel
they don't realize that though they just
come in they see the patient has been
completely covered
and I finally had some peace and quiet
hours
cuz I signed a DNR that's that's how you
get sleep in a hospital put your snorkel
on put the sheet over your ad get some
slate they actually the mother one I
have is faa-approved
that's awesome I get on a plane I'm
sitting down you know we're getting
ready to fly if I get crunched in there
right I put on that mask before the
flight starts and the guy next to me is
like what's that he saw I don't die
my name is Massimo how are you
yeah when I wake up maybe
I do like to mess with people so my
favorite things to do
I had this Dodge Challenger 2010 model
with the you know the the little thing
popped out of the hood I'm not a big car
guy that I like dry though yeah it
looked cool it's like a Dukes of Hazzard
kind of car it was all black and this
cop is behind me when we're at Hardee's
I'm going through the line it's like you
know a people deep and we're going to
round the corner and every time the car
moves ahead of me I pop the clutch just
because I can and the cop is like
catskill he's right behind me the whole
time I'm doing like eight times it's
like the slowest car chase ever we get
into the window and it's like if she
says hey we got a problem we're at a
Coke Zero what you want to drink I was
like I don't care what you got just
bored of the bag fast I'm getting chased
by the cops she throws my food
most people in South Georgia still talk
about those
I like at Christmastime to go to malls
like I really you know the busy mall
around where we live and and I look for
that super spot you know the one that's
closest to the the food court that
everybody wants you know and I'll go
there for my lunch break but I'll go
ahead and get some food and just do this
on my lunch
you know just find the perfect parking
spot pull in put it in reverse and just
put my foot on the brake and eat a
sandwich
it's pretty awesome actually move the
mirror just thing you see the perfect
angle of people driving by it's like
fishing you catch one I get to see him
go through all these slows levels of you
know emotions like surprise and elated
and Confused
sad right at that point you got to let
off the brake just a little bit I won't
follow you pull back you got away better
you pull right back I can get away with
it cuz I'm big right he's so mad at me
always make sure my kid was with me in
his little car seats when I'm doing in
case you know that gets all mad I'll get
out hey man how you doing a pole the
killer cars I can't attack you today
that's my less I don't wear you know
bulletproof vest I just a kid and it's
not even a real kid it's just this doll
I have in the travel he's grown now my
oldest child who's five years old man we
had a fun time we went to McDonald's and
the manager was just having a bad day
right you could tell that it's like this
you know kind of take your order just
like just man and it doesn't take me any
time at all to process oh I'm gonna mess
with this person so there I am my five
year old kid we're trying to get
something to eat at McDonald's and this
guy's old man rayji
I said yeah I'll take you know the big
and taste to you and everyone
[Music]
and that's gibberish just so you know I
have no idea as a small child when we
left your hon and I never coached him
into this I just thought it'd be funny
if I did that and he looked at me
you wanted a one-up bees
just until he hyperventilated you know
finally stop once the cheeseburger happy
we'll catch up wrong
for real my guys a hard language hey did
you know that Drybar comedy has their
own app download it right now to watch
save and share clips and watch my whole
special